realestate.co.nz 2006-05-04

# New Zealand Real Estate Listing Service

RealENZ is a website providing a searchable online database of properties for sale throughout New Zealand in conjunction with the Real Estate Institute of New Zealand and is an advertising service to licensed real estate agents. 

1\. Cookies   
No personal information is collected by our use of cookies. Cookies are used solely for the purposes of efficient navigation. The RealENZ website may use cookies and log file information (such as Internet Protocol Address, referring urls, etc.) about your activity at this site in order to understand Web site usage and enhance your experience at this site.  No cookie or log file information is linked with any personal information you may have provided at the Web site. You can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser and/or deleting them from your hard drive but some parts of our website may not be available or may function incorrectly if cookies are refused. 

2\. Property Finder   
When you sign up with the Property Finder alert on this site, RealENZ will use that email address to deliver the property information you have requested. To delete your information, revisit the Property Finder function on the RealENZ website or contact us on: [realenz@realenz.co.nz](mailto:realenz@realenz.co.nz)   Personal information recorded by people registering with our Property Finder product will not be passed on to any other company or individual. 

3\. Contact information   
Contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address, for consumers, investors or customers with questions, concerns, complaints, inquires, requests for information or technical support questions, is used to respond to your request for information. Such data is usually deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business, but can be amended or deleted upon request. To review, amend, or delete your information, contact: [realenz@realenz.co.nz](mailto:realenz@realenz.co.nz)   
Please provide your name and contact information and the approximate date you contacted us. 

4\. Ad Delivery   
>In most cases, when you see an internet ad, RealENZ has been asked by the website to act as a marketing agent for ad delivery or reporting.  The information RealENZ possesses on such a web site's behalf belongs to that website and is not further used by RealENZ or other companies.   
RealENZ does not collect information or develop marketing scores that indicate a user's individual health condition, detailed financial information, sexual orientation or behaviour, information that appears to relate to children under 13, racial and ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical opinions, and trade union membership. 

5\. Third Party Ad Servers   
We use third party companies to serve advertisements when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites, including information gathered by cookies, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

6\. Policy changes   
RealENZ may change its policy as new products are added or old ones are changed, but RealENZ treats personal information in a manner consistent with the policy under which it was collected, unless we have your consent to use it differently. If part or all of RealENZ's businesses are sold or transferred, we will take steps to assure that these same principles apply. 

7\. Questions and complaints   
Questions, concerns, comments and complaints can be emailed to: [realenz@realenz.co.nz](mailto:realenz@realenz.co.nz)   
RealENZ Ltd, PO Box 9284, Newmarket, Auckland, New Zealand. 

8\. Security   
RealENZ has implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Our employees are made aware of and are accountable for compliance with our privacy policy.
